(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-04T22:54:56.094228",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
[Please wait a moment for the show to begin]
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆ
Okayu
ころね
Korone
ミオ
Mio
Are you ready?
No!
Perfect!
G-A-M-E-R-S
Good!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
[Please wait a while until the event begins]
ミオ
Mio
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆ
Okayu
ころね
Korone
Are you ready? Go!
Go!
フブキ
Fubuki
G-A-M-E-R-S
フブキ
Fubuki
G-A-M-E-R-S
オカユ
Okayu
コロネ
Korone
Are you ready?
G-A-M-E-R-S
フブキ
Fubuki
ミオ
Mio
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the event begins
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆ
Okayu
ころね
Korone
Are you ready?
Perfect
G-A-M-E-R-S
フブキ
Fubuki
ミオ
Mio
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆ
Okayu
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the show begins.
コロネ
Korone
Are you ready?
Perfect
Hey! Hey!
ミオ
Mio
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆ
Okayu
コロネ
Korone
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment for the performance to start.
ホロライブ ゲーマーズ！！！！
Hololive GAMERS!!!!
(G.A.M.E.R.S)
We are GAMERS!!!!
こーん！とキツネが登場
Kon! A fox makes her entrance!
白髪ケモミミ 白上フブキです
White-haired with animal ears, I'm Shirakami Fubuki!
スッ込んじゃ始まらない
Nothing starts if you stay hiding in the back!
君もスコーン部に入部しなさい
You should join the Sukon-bu too!
Hi Friends!! (Yeah!!)
古今東西 コーン茶をちょうだい
From all times and places, please give me corn tea!
AIじゃないし 得意はMC
I'm not an AI, and my specialty is MCing!
赤い恋より金の鯉が推し
Rather than red love, my favorite is the golden carp!
うち うち うちだよ 大神ミオだよ
It's me, it's me, it's Ookami Mio!
黒髪ケモミミ狼 (みおーん！)
Black-haired beast-eared wolf! (Mioon!)
ツッコんで止めます like a Mama
I'll jump in and stop you, like a Mama!
笑い出すと止まらない ゲラゲラ
Once I start laughing I can't stop, chuckle chuckle!
つまり実はPONってコト！？
So basically, that means I'm actually a klutz?!
小足ステップしちゃう音
The sound of tiptoeing steps!
タロット占いを見る未来
Foreseeing the future with tarot fortune-telling!
ホラーゲームはやりなくなぁい！
I don't wanna play horror games!
4人揃えば ゲーマーズ最強
When the four of us gather, Gamers are the strongest!
君も遊ぼうよ Bダッシュ
Come play with us too, B-dash!
クリア目指して レベル上げ
Leveling up to reach the stage clear!
今日は何プレイしよう
What shall we play today?
君のハートも 攻略しちゃう
We'll conquer your heart too!
選択をして シミュレーション
Make your choice in this simulation!
初見も古参も 対よろ
First-timers and veterans alike, let's have a good game!
やっぱりゲームは 楽しいね
After all, games are so much fun!
(G.A.M.E.R.S)
We are GAMERS!!!!
いっくよー もぐもぐ～ 猫又おかゆ
Here I go~ Mogu mogu~ Nekomata Okayu!
おにぎり おにぎりは ぃっどうぞー
Rice balls, rice balls, here you go~
きらきら ふらふら
Sparkling and wandering around...
しゃ～ない猫だもん
Can't be helped, I'm a cat after all!
ふーん そっかぁ 僕でよくない？
Hmm, I see. Wouldn't I be good enough?
まったり ゆっくり 跳ねるリズム
Relaxed and easygoing, a bouncing rhythm!
全 肯定 する おかゆ イズム
Total validation, that's Okayu-ism!
全 行程 効率 OK
All processes, efficiency OK!
毎日 僕と いっしょ！
Together with me every day!
ぉぁょ～ ゆびゆび ワンワン
Good morning~ Yubi yubi, woof woof!
パンをコネコネ 戌神ころね
Kneading bread, Inugami Korone!
犬種：キャバリア・キング・チャールズ・スパニエル
Breed: Cavalier King Charles Spaniel!
懐く けど圧かける
Affectionate, but applying pressure!
訛るイントネーション
Accented intonation!
割れる リアクション
Screaming, ear-splitting reactions!
まずは指を捧げてくれる？ 配信ショー
First, will you offer your fingers? Stream show!
わがったなー ほーね 指示 厨おけ
Got it, bone! Backseat gamers welcome!
好物 のレトロゲー お届け
Delivering my favorite retro games!
4人揃えば ゲーマーズ最高
When the four of us gather, Gamers are the best!
フラグが立てば すぐ回収
Setting up flags and resolving them right away!
エイム鍛えて 狙い撃ち
Training our aim, taking the shot!
今日は何プレイしよう
What shall we play today?
君のハートを 回復しちゃう
We'll restore your heart!
ワクワクするね このダンジョン
This dungeon is so exciting!
"耐久"っていうか 止められない
It's an endurance stream—we can't be stopped!
だって ゲームが 好き なんだもん
'Cause we just love games so much!
突然ですが、ボーナスチャレンジの時間です。
Suddenly, it's time for a Bonus Challenge!
大きな声でレスポンスをして高得点を狙いましょう！
Let's give a big shout back and aim for a high score!
Say!! こーん こんっ！
Say!! Kon kon!
(こーん こんっ！)
(Kon kon!)
Say!! みおーん みおん！
Say!! Mioon mion!
(みおーん みおん！)
(Mioon mion!)
Say!! もぐっ もぐっ！
Say!! Mogu mogu!
(もぐっ もぐっ！)
(Mogu mogu!)
Say!! ゆびっ ゆびっ！
Say!! Yubi yubi!
(ゆびっ ゆびっ！)
(Yubi yubi!)
Say!! こーん こんっ！
Say!! Kon kon!
(こーん こんっ！)
(Kon kon!)
Say!! みおーん みおん！
Say!! Mioon mion!
(みおーん みおん！)
(Mioon mion!)
Say!! もぐっ もぐっ！
Say!! Mogu mogu!
(もぐっ もぐっ！)
(Mogu mogu!)
Say!! ゆびっ ゆびっ！
Say!! Yubi yubi!
(ゆびっ ゆびっ！)
(Yubi yubi!)
4人揃えば ゲーマーズ最強
When the four of us gather, Gamers are the strongest!
上手く行かなくても コンティニュー
Even if things don't go well, continue!
全クリするまで 諦めない
Won't give up until 100% completion!
エンディングを 見に行こう
Let's go watch the ending roll!
君のハートも 攻略しちゃう
We'll conquer your heart too!
選択をして シミュレーション
Make your choice in this simulation!
初見も古参も 対よろ
First-timers and veterans alike, good game!
やっぱりゲームは 楽しいね
After all, games are so much fun!
(G.A.M.E.R.S) We are GAMERS!!!!
こうして世界に 平和が訪れたのだ――
And thus, peace returned to the world...
本日もいっぱいでございますな！
It's packed again today!
ありがたいですね！本当ありがたい！
We're so grateful! Truly grateful!
ということで！
And so!
さあ、始まりました！ホロライブゲーマーズフェス
Here we go! Hololive Gamers Fes!
超超超超ゲーマーズ2
Cho-Cho-Cho-Cho Gamers 2...
DAY 2でーす！
Day 2!
ということで皆さん、コンコンきーつね！
So everyone, Kon-kon-kitsune!
狐です、どうもー！
It's the fox here, hello!
なぜかゲーマーズで手漕ぎボートを4人漕がされてた白上よー。よしよーし。
I'm Shirakami, who somehow made all 4 Gamers row a rowboat. There, there.
手漕ぎボート漕がされたんだ？
You made us row a rowboat?
練習の時あんなの1回もしなかった！
We didn't do anything like that in rehearsal!
とっさにね！
It was pure instinct!
とっさになんだ！
Pure instinct, huh!
はーい！続いてはー？
Okay! Who's next?
はい！
Yes!
うち、うち、うちだよー！
It's me, me, me!
大神ミオだよー！
It's Ookami Mio!
緑がいっぱい！
So much green!
大神ミオの皆さん、今日も盛り上げよろしくお願いいたします！
Everyone here for Ookami Mio, let me hear you cheer today!
そしてー？
And next?
はーい！
Here!
みんな行くよー！
Here we go, everyone!
マークまぐー！
Mogu mogu~
よく出来ましたー！
Very well done!
どうも、ホロライブゲーマーズの猫又おかゆです！
Hello, I'm Nekomata Okayu from Hololive Gamers!
今日もよろしくお願いします。あの、出禁にならないようにね
Glad to be here today. I'll do my best so I don't get banned...
頑張ります！
I'll give it my all!
そしてー？
And next?
はーい！みんな行くよー！
Okay! Here we go, everyone!
じゃん！けん！
Rock! Paper!
ぽん！
Scissors!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
戌神ころねです！よろしくお願いします！
I'm Inugami Korone! Nice to meet you all!
え、オータニ翔平の次かい！
Wait, after Shohei Ohtani?!
サザエさんじゃん！サザエさんだったよ！
That was Sazae-san! You did Sazae-san!
サザエさんだよー！
It's Sazae-san!
サザエさんかい！
Sazae-san, really?!
ってことでね！
So anyway!
それでもみんな平気だった？今大丈夫だった？
Was everyone okay with that? Was that fine?
ついてこれてるみたいみんな！
Looks like everyone kept up!
流石です！
As expected!
ということで改めまして、ホロライブゲーマーズフェス
So once again, Hololive Gamers Fes...
超超超超ゲーマーズ2 DAY 2が
Cho-Cho-Cho-Cho Gamers 2 Day 2...
ここさいたまスーパーアリーナで開幕じゃー！
Begins right here at Saitama Super Arena!
いやーなんと！
Wow, believe it or not!
DAY 1、DAY 2合わせると約3万5千人以上が！
Combining Day 1 and Day 2, over 35,000 people are attending!
そして今日のDAY 2はなんと、1万7千人ぐらいいるらしいですよ！
And for today's Day 2, there are about 17,000 people here!
すごい！上の方もみんな！
Amazing! Everyone up in the upper levels too!
いますよー！あそこまでいっぱいー！
You're all there! It's full all the way up!
見えてる？そこー！
Can you see us over there?
見えてるー！
We see you!
大丈夫ですー！
Everything's good!
左右も見えてますかー？
Can you see on the left and right too?
見えてるかなー？
I wonder if they can see us?
すごいですよー！
This is incredible!
去年はね、ミオが来れなかった国立代々木競技場第一体育館だったんですけども
Last year, Mio couldn't come to the National Yoyogi Stadium First Gymnasium, but...
さらに今回は大きな場所でやらせていただくことになりました！
This time, we get to perform at an even bigger venue!
2回目やらせていただけて本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for letting us host this a second time!
4人揃って立つことができました！
All four of us are able to stand here together!
よかったよかった！みんなのおかげぞ！ありがとうございます！
So glad! It's all thanks to everyone! Thank you!
さて、改めましてこのイベントではですね
Now then, once again, at this event...
ゲームが大好きな我々を中心に
Centered around us game-loving members...
超超超超豪華なゲストの皆さんと
Along with super, super gorgeous guests...
様々なゲームタイトルに挑戦したり、ライブパフォーマンスをお届けするプレミアムイベントとなってまーす！
This premium event features game challenges and live performances!
しかも今回ですね、皆様おわかりかと思いますが
Plus, as I'm sure you've all noticed...
DAY 1に引き続き4人の
Continuing from Day 1, all four of us have...
おそろい新衣装ー！
Matching new outfits!
尻尾サービスね！尻尾サービス中！
Tail service! Tail service in progress!
さあ、さらに会場ではですね、一部撮影OKなパートがありますので
Also, in the venue, there will be sections where photos are allowed!
そちらもお楽しみに！
So look forward to that too!
最後まで皆さん、盛り上がっていけますかー！？
Are you all ready to stay hyped until the end?!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
ということでね、我々ゲーマーズからも1人ずつ意気込みを言っていきたいと思いますよ！
So each of us Gamers will share our enthusiasm!
では、最初ー！まずはミオから！
First up, let's start with Mio!
はい！
Yes!
えーっとですね
Well, um...
昨日のあの意気込みで、あの明日まで体調を崩さないように頑張るっていう風にね
Yesterday when sharing my enthusiasm, I said I'd do my best not to get sick until tomorrow.
言わせていただいたんですけれども
That's what I said, but...
もう今日あのこの会場にね、あのもう居て、ここのステージに立つということは
Since I'm already at this venue today and standing on this stage...
どんなに体調崩そうとも帰れないということなんですよね！
...it means no matter how sick I get, I can't go home!
体調崩さないで！ダメダメ！
Don't get sick! No, no!
あ、無理はせずね！
Ah, without overdoing it!
最後まで笑顔で走り切る！頑張りたいと思います！みんな一緒に盛り上がっていこう！
So, I'll do my best to run all the way to the end with a smile! Let's all get hyped together!
続いては、おかゆ！
Next up, Okayu!
はい！
Yes!
まあ、昨日はね、打率3割を目標に大谷翔平ね
Well, yesterday, aim for a .300 batting average like Shohei Ohtani...
頑張ったんですけど
...I gave it my best, but...
ちょっと逆に頑張りすぎて微妙に出禁になりかけたので
...I overdid it a bit and almost got banned...
今日はほどほどに、逆にほどほどに楽しんでいきたいと思います！
...so today, I want to take it moderately, enjoying myself at a steady pace!
どれくらいなんですか、ほどほどは？
How much is "moderate"?
2.5！
2.5!
昨日なんかギスギスしてて白上がすごい被害を被る内容を受けたんですけど
Yesterday felt so tense and Shirakami ended up taking a lot of damage...
なんかすりつけるとかさ
...like placing the blame on me or something.
何だっけ？
What was that again?
センシティブやらされたりとか
...making me do sensitive stuff...
ほんとに？どんなんでしたっけ？
Really? What was it like?
打率3割だろっていうことやらされたんですけど
You made me do that whole ".300 batting average" thing!
やんないよ！
I'm not doing that!
ツーペアで打たされたりさ...
Getting hit on a two pair...
可愛かったよ！
You were cute!
可愛くないよな！
No I wasn't!
満足度は高かったです。
The satisfaction was high.
大谷さんの話をしていただいた...
You were talking about Ohtani...
はい！ころね！
Yes! Korone!
昨日はね、ちょっと翔平のためにとか言って
Yesterday I said things like "For Shohei"...
1部のコロニキがね
...and some of the Coro-niki...
ビビビッて過敏になってたので
...were getting super sensitive and uneasy...
今日はコロニキのために頑張りまーす！
...so today, I'll do my best for the Coro-niki!
あ、可愛い！
Ah, so cute!
喜んでるよ、みんな！
Everyone's so happy!
翔平ごめーん！
Shohei, I'm sorry!
やめて！
Stop it!
はい！そして白上もですね...
Yes! And Shirakami too...
今日もですね、たくさん読み上げることが多いと思うんですけども
Today as well, I think there's a lot of announcements to read...
その間ね、この3人がきっといっぱい面白おかしいことやってくれるんじゃないかと思っておりますので
...but during that time, I'm sure these three will do lots of funny and hilarious things...
白上のお話にも耳を傾けつつ、お目目はね、上の大きいモニターと
...so while listening to Shirakami speak with your ears, keep your eyes on the big monitor above...
そして可愛い3人を見ていただいて、最後みんなで笑って帰れるといいなと思ってます！よろしくお願いします！
...and watch these cute three, so we can all go home with a laugh at the end! Please enjoy!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you!
さあ！そして昨日と今日行われる「超超超超ゲーマーズ2」はABEMA PPVで生配信してます！
Now! The "Cho-Cho-Cho-Cho Gamers 2" held yesterday and today is live streaming on ABEMA PPV!
コメントのみんな見えてるよ〜！
Everyone in the comments, we can see you~!
見えてるよ〜！
We see you~!
「翔平見てる〜？」って草
"Is Shohei watching?" LOL
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
配信チケットは絶賛発売中です！
Streaming tickets are now on sale!
イベントが終わっても8月4日(月)の23:59まで何度でも見返すことができます！
Even after the event ends, you can rewatch it as many times as you like until Monday, August 4th at 23:59!
購入特典として、DAY1とDAY2で異なるシチュエーションの限定オリジナルボイスドラマが付いてきます！
As a purchase bonus, a limited original voice drama with different situations for DAY 1 and DAY 2 is included!
DAY1は「ヒミツの事前プロデュース」ボイス！
DAY 1 is the "Secret Pre-Production" voice!
ヒミツ？
Secret?
そしてDAY2は「ナイショの反省会」！
And DAY 2 is "Secret Reflection Meeting"!
ナイショ？どの程度ナイショなんですか？
Secret? How secret is secret?
めっちゃナイショです！
Super secret!
怪しいものではない！とってもセンシティブです！
It's nothing sketchy! It's very sensitive!
えぇー？！
What?!
はい！あとはですね、我々からの手書きメッセージ入りのライブ画像も付いてきますので、ぜひチェックしてみてください！
Yes! Also, live photos with handwritten messages from us are included, so please check them out!
よろしくお願いします！
Please check it out!
さらに昨年度行われました「超超超超ゲーマーズ」のダイジェスト映像がABEMAプレミアムで公開中です！
Furthermore, digest footage of last year's "Cho-Cho-Cho-Cho Gamers" is now available on ABEMA Premium!
昨年のね、楽しかった場をちょっと見ようは、見逃せないんですけども、3人でもね、頑張らせていただきましたので、その様子いっぱい見てください！
You shouldn't miss seeing how fun last year was, and even with 3 members we worked hard, so please watch a lot of it!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you!
はい！さらにさらに！イベント公式グッズの受注販売が開始中です！
Yes! And furthermore! Pre-orders for official event merchandise are now open!
こちらの期間は7月21日の23:59まで！
The pre-order period lasts until July 21st at 23:59!
Cyber Goods Storeにて受付中で、10月中旬頃からお届けです！
Accepting orders on Cyber Goods Store, shipping from around mid-October!
こちらも予約したよって人いますかー？
Is there anyone who already pre-ordered?
あ、いるいる！結構買ってるんじゃない？
Ah, there are! Quite a few bought it, right?
ネット通販ありがとうございます！
Thank you for using online shopping!
そしてですね、会場販売のグッズはすべて完売と聞いております！みなさんありがとうございましたー！
And we heard that all on-site merchandise has completely sold out! Thank you everyone!
すごい！完売？！
Amazing! Sold out?!
びっくりしました、みなさん本当に！ランダムで推しゲットできたかい？
We were so surprised, really! Were you all able to get your favorite through the random items?
「ゲットできなかった」という方がいらっしゃいましたら
If there are any of you who couldn't get them,
事後通販で受注販売しておりますのでゲットしてください！
they're available via post-event mail order, so please get them!
そしてさらに！ご存知の方もいらっしゃると思いますが
And furthermore, as some of you may already know,
NTTドコモさんのhome 5Gとのコラボキャンペーン実施中でーす！
our collab campaign with NTT Docomo's home 5G is underway!
あ、致しましただねこれ。実施終わっちゃったんだ！
Ah, it was underway... Wait, it already ended!
でかタオルや入り口でもらえるうちわ、皆さんゲットしましたかー？
Did everyone get the giant towel and the fan given at the entrance?
ちゃんとやりましたよって人ー！
Raise your hand if you got them!
おっ、いらっしゃいます！ありがとうございます！
Oh, there are people! Thank you so much!
安全にして最後までお楽しみくださーい！
Stay safe and enjoy until the very end!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
あ、すみません！こちら事後限定グッズとしまして
Ah, excuse me! Speaking of post-event exclusive goods,
アクリルパネルが追加されてるんですよ！皆さん知ってましたー？
an acrylic panel has actually been added! Did everyone know?
そう！実はアクリルパネル！
That's right! An acrylic panel!
こちらね、事後限定グッズなので
Since this is a post-event exclusive item,
今「あ、そういえば！」って思った方は全員とも、ぜひゲットしてください！
anyone thinking "Ah, right!" right now, please go ahead and get one!
あの、あの… やめてー！
Um, um... Stop it!
ごめんなさい！
I'm sorry!
まだまだ続きますからねー！
There's still more to come!
「我々ゲーマーズを応援したい」という声が多かったので
Since many requested to support us Gamers,
今回のイベントでCheerSPOTさんとのコラボ決定ー！
a collaboration with CheerSPOT has been decided for this event!
誰でも簡単に、好きなCheerSPOTの場所に我々の応援広告を出すことができます！
Anyone can easily post support ads for us at any CheerSPOT location!
白上も割と日頃利用させていただいておりますので…
Shirakami uses it quite often as well...
めっちゃ嬉しいですね！
That makes us so happy!
この会場でも設置してあるのを見たと思うんですけども
I'm sure you saw them set up here at this venue too,
あんな感じですごく綺麗に広告出せますので、よければよろしくお願いします！
but you can post ads very nicely like that, so please check it out!
さらに！さいたまスーパーアリーナ会場内で、等身大を初お披露目させていただきました！
Furthermore, we unveiled our life-sized figures inside Saitama Super Arena!
3月のEXPO会場で発表されたフブミオ等身大に続きまして、
Following the FubuMio life-sized figures announced at the EXPO in March,
おかころのフィギュアも発表されました！見てくれましたかー？
Okayu and Korone's figures were also announced! Did you see them?
見てくれたー？ 可愛い！
Did you see them? They're so cute!
また昨日から新作フィギュアはDesign COCOから受注開始ということで、
Also, pre-orders for the new figures started yesterday on Design COCO,
皆さん、予約しましたかー？
so did everyone pre-order them?
したー！
We did!
めっちゃ可愛かった！めちゃくちゃ可愛かったよね！
They were so cute! Super duper cute!
イベントの開催を記念しまして、8月7日までに
To commemorate this event, if you pre-order by August 7th,
公式で予約してくれた方には特典のステッカープレゼントだそうです！
you will receive a bonus sticker as a gift!
欲しい！欲しい！
I want it! I want it!
そしてね、おかころも出たんですけども、フブミオが終わっちゃったと思ってたんですが、
And although OkaKoro came out, for those who thought FubuMio was over,
なんと期間限定でフブミオの追加予約も開始してます！
additional pre-orders for FubuMio have started for a limited time!
最高！お願いします！
Awesome! Please get them!
ぜひともゲーマーズ4人揃えられる方は揃えてみろー！
If you can collect all four Gamers members, try collecting us all!
さて最後に！カンダフル様による協賛企業グッズ！
Now lastly! Sponsored goods from Candaful!
超超超超ポップコーンと、超超超超グリルチキンでーす！
Super-super-super-super popcorn and super-super-super-super grilled chicken!
今回のイベントのキービジュアルが全面に出たデザインとなっているとのことでして、
The design features the main key visual of this event prominently,
ポップコーンは税込1,000円、缶詰は税込1,500円で販売でーす！
popcorn is ¥1,000 (tax incl.) and the canned chicken is ¥1,500 (tax incl.)!
ポップコーンは塩キャラメル味！缶詰はグリルチキンになってまーす！
Popcorn is salted caramel flavor! Canned food is grilled chicken!
ポップコーンの方にはランダムトレカが付いてるそうなのでよろしくお願いします！
Popcorn comes with a random trading card, so please check it out!
食べてもー！ なんと！
Eat it, eat it! What?!
Cyber Goods Storeではこちらのポップコーンと缶詰が完売になってしまった！
At the Cyber Goods Store, these popcorn and canned chicken items sold out!
えぇー！？ 何ですってー！？
Whaaat!? You're kidding!
なんと本日22時から追加販売が決定しましたー！
But additional sales have been decided starting tonight at 10 PM!
イェーイ！
Yay!
こちらのグッズはですね、他のグッズと異なりまして、
Unlike the other merchandise, these items
受注販売ではなく数量限定商品のためご注意ください！
are limited quantity items, not made-to-order, so please be careful!
Cyber Goods Storeの他にカンダフルの公式通販サイトでも販売してますので皆さんチェックをお願いします！
Besides Cyber Goods Store, they're also on Candaful's official site, so please check them out!
集合アクリルパネルも含めてですね、事後でしか購入できないグッズなので、皆さんぜひ確認してください！
Including the group acrylic panel, these are post-event exclusives, so please make sure to check!
なんかすごい気視感… デジャブ？
I feel a strong sense of deja vu... Deja vu?
まぁまぁ、おいで！ゲーマーズ列車に乗ろう！ 出発！
Come on, get on the Gamers train! Depart!
フブミオ駅！出発！出発！
FubuMio Station! Depart! Depart!
いってらっしゃい！ 終点！終点！ 終わっちゃった！
Have a nice trip! Last stop! Last stop! It's already over!
えー、また昨日に引き続きまして、本日も韓国でのライブビューイングが開催されてまーす！
Following yesterday, today also has a live viewing in South Korea!
韓国の皆さん、見えてますかー？
Everyone in Korea, can you see us?
アンニョンハセヨ〜！ カムサハムニダ〜！
Annyeonghaseyo~! Kamsahamnida~!
韓国の方もですね、終わった後とか始まる前とかに集合写真いっぱい撮ってくださってて、
Everyone in Korea took lots of group photos before and after the event,
ポスト確認させていただきました！今日もよろしくお願いします！
and we checked your posts! Please enjoy today too!
サランヘヨー！
Saranghaeyo~!
ゲームタイトル発表していきましょうかね？
Shall we announce the game title?
はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes!
はい、じゃあ行きますよー！せーのー！
Okay, here we go! Ready, set...
ドン！
Bam!
Gang Beasts
はい！こちらはゼリーのようにぐにゃぐにゃのキャラクターたちが、危険なステージでドタバタの乱闘を繰り広げる、ちょっとおバカなマルチプレイヤーパーティーゲームです！
This is a silly multiplayer party game where squishy, jelly-like characters engage in slapstick brawls on dangerous stages!
今回は2対2のチーム戦と個人戦の2マッチで対決したいと思います！
This time, we'll compete in two matches: a 2-on-2 team battle and an individual battle!
こちら勝利すると、頭の後ろにですね、星のバルーンがつきます！
When you win, a star balloon will be attached behind your head!
最終的にバルーンが一番多い人が勝利となります！
In the end, the person with the most balloons wins!
ということで早速やっていきますよー！ゴーゴーゴー！
So, let's get right into it! Go, go, go!
最初のマッチは2対2のチーム戦ということで、
The first match is a 2-on-2 team battle,
チームはそうですね、先ほどあみだで決めました。
and the teams were decided earlier by an Amida lottery.
フブおかチームと、ミオころチーム！
The FubuOka team, and the MioKoro team!
ということで、こちら...
And so, for ours...
ふたりは神様！バンプキンズ！
We are gods! Bumpkins!
合ってるかな？ 合ってる合ってる！
Is that right? It's right, it's right!
多分ギリギリ合ってる。ギリギリ！
It's probably barely right. Barely!
ということで、こちらで対決していきたいと思います！
So, we're going to face off with these teams!
な、なんか...なんか無いくらいですか？
U-Uh... don't you guys have anything?
え？何がですか？
Huh? What do you mean?
え、なんかこう、掛け声とかチーム名とか...
You know, like a chant or a team name...
ありますよ！
We have one!
え、じゃあ教えてください！
Oh, then please tell us!
まずは... まずは？
First... First?
まずお姉ちゃんのおかゆーさん！
First, for my big sister, Okayu-san!
もーっと！フブちゃんです！
And even more! Fubu-chan is here!
ふたり合わせて、ギャングキンズ！
Together, we are Gangkins!
さっきのやつですか？
Is that the same one as before?
ダメです！ダメだったんかい！
No good! So it wasn't good earlier?!
なんか弱み握られてない？握られてたかも。
Are they holding something against you? Maybe they are.
イベントの空気に流されている...
We're getting carried away by the event's atmosphere...
ほら、準備できたから！後ろにコントローラーが...
Look, we're ready! Controllers are behind us...
コントローラー持ちますよー！自分のだ、自分のだ！
Let's grab controllers! Get yours, get yours!
自分のカラーとってね、ちゃんと。
Make sure to pick your own color.
はい！ということで。持った！持った！
Alright, so... Got it, got it!
コントローラーでやっていきたいと思います！
We'll be playing with our controllers!
では、ゲーム画面切り替えておいてください！はいー！
Now, please switch to the game screen! Yes!
なんか両手あげてますけど(笑)
They're raising both hands though!
これ誰が誰だか...みんなわかんないのかな？
Does everyone know who is who?
じゃあ簡単に紹介しよう！
Then let's introduce them briefly!
青くて白衣着てるのが、どうやら白上さんだそうです。どうもどうも。
The blue one wearing a lab coat seems to be Shirakami-san. Hello, hello.
探してそのお隣、猫の被り物をかぶってるのが僕です！
And next to her, the one wearing a cat mask is me!
はい、おかゆー！
Yes, Okayu!
えっとなんか真っ赤っかで、ネコミミっぽいのがあるのがうちです。大神です。
Um, the bright red one with cat-like ears is me. I'm Ookami.
「ギャッハー！」みたいなやつがころね！
The one going "Gyahaha!" is Korone!
ということで、まずは赤と青に分かれましたチーム戦でございます！
So first, we have a team battle split into Red and Blue!
準備いいですか？はい！はい！
Are you ready? Yes! Yes!
それでは、Gang Beasts 1回戦！スタート！
Then, Gang Beasts round 1! Start!
やるぞー！頑張るぞー！
Let's do this! Let's do our best!
大丈夫かこれー？ 頑張る！今の力を見せてやろう！
Is this gonna be okay? Do your best! Let me show you my skills!
いけるのか？ いけるよ！うまいんだから任せて！
Can you do it? I can! I'm good at this, leave it to me!
赤！赤！ 青で行くよー！
Red! Red! Let's go with Blue!
ファイト！おらー！ 捕まえた！捕まえた！
Fight! Oraa! Gotcha! Gotcha!
やばい！おらおらおら！ いやー！助けてー！
Oh no! Ora ora ora! Nooo! Help!
なんか狭い！狭い！ 穴が開いた！ ギャー！
It's so narrow! A hole opened! Gyaa!
いやー！ やばいやばいやばい！
Nooo! Oh no, oh no, oh no!
あっ！あっ！待って！ やめろー！
Ah! Ah! Wait! Stop it!
いいえ！ 何これ？！ やめろー！
No! What is this?! Stop it!
やめろー！ いやー！やめろー！
Stop it! Nooo! Stop it!
あー！ やばいやばいやばい！
Ahhh! Oh no, oh no, oh no!
ギャー！ いやー！
Gyaa! Nooo!
いやー！ ぎゃー！
Nooo! Gyaa!
落ちる！落ちる！ 痛い！ あー！
I'm gonna fall! Ouch! Ahhh!
あー！おらー！ やばいやばい！
Ahhh! Oraa! Oh no, oh no!
やばい！やばい！グニャグニャしてる！
Oh no! Oh no! It's so squishy!
こんなの...待って！おかゆ、どこー？
This is... Wait! Okayu, where are you?
手伝って！ 誰もいない！誰もいないよー！
Help me! No one's here! Nobody's here!
うわー！何やってんのー？！
Uwaa! What are you doing?!
ギャー！ 待ってー！
Gyaa! Wait!
もう死んじゃったー！ 待って！ 死なないで、ミオー！
I'm already dead! Wait! Don't die, Mio!
やばいやばいやばい！みちづれだー！
Oh no, oh no, oh no! Taking you down with me!
あははは！勝ったー！
Ahahaha! We won!
ナイス、ナイス！やったー！
Nice, nice! Yay!
あー！でもこれ...
Ah! But this...
2先なので、2回勝ったチームが勝利ですからね！
It's best of three, so the team that wins twice is the victor!
おー！よしー！星だー！
Oh! All right! It's a star!
ブルーの勝利
[Blue's Victory]
勝った！勝ったー！
We won! We won!
数の暴力やばい！
The strength in numbers is crazy!
痛ーい！
Ouch!
次は頑張れるよ！
We can do better next time!
ピンチ！
We're in a pinch!
やばいやばい！
Oh no, oh no!
ゴミ箱から逃げようと...
Trying to escape from the trash bin...
穴の中へ...
Into the hole...
助けてー！
Save me!
ミオをやれ！
Get Mio!
ブルーの勝利
[Blue's Victory]
やったー！勝ったー！
Yay! We won!
また負けたー！
We lost again!
位置ずれのミオんだ
It's Mion with the lag displacement.
負けたよー！
We lost!
うそー！
No way!
はい！ということで！
Alright, so with that...
星の数は～...
The number of stars is...
1、2、3、4！
1, 2, 3, 4!
2人合わせて4点！
4 points for the two of us combined!
一方～...
On the other hand...
こっち102個！
We have 102!
数えてない！数えてない！
You didn't count that! You didn't count that!
ということで、今回は...
And so, this time...
4対2で、負けー！
At 4 to 2, it's our loss!
勝者です！
We are the winners!
唐突ですが、ここでお知らせでございます！
It's sudden, but we have an announcement here!
バイバーイ！早っ！
Bye-bye! So fast!
無料配信をご覧の皆様はここまでとなります！
That's all for those watching the free stream!
続きをご覧になりたい方は、ぜひABEMA PPVにてチケットを購入お願いします！
If you'd like to see the rest, please purchase a ticket on ABEMA PPV!
お願いします！
Please do!
この後、個人戦が待ってますからね！
The individual matches are coming up next!
バチバチにやっていきたいと思いますよ！
We're going to give it all we've got!
それでは、またねー！バイバワーイ！
Well then, see you later! Bye-byewai!
無料パートは終了いたしました 全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
[The free part has ended. The full event is available on ABEMA PPV!]
無料パートは終了いたしました
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The free portion of the stream has ended.
Watch the full event on ABEMA PPV!
無料パートは終了いたしました
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The free part has ended.
Watch the full event on ABEMA PPV!
無料パートは終了いたしました 全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The free portion has ended. Watch the full event on ABEMA PPV!
ころね
Korone
無料パートは終了いたしました 全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The free portion has ended. Watch the full event on ABEMA PPV!